Guide to the Darinka Archive 1973-2010 MSS 340
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries D: Additional Sound Recordings
    - Workdogs Old, 1994 (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
    - Al Jolson: Al Jolson Souvenir Album, 1953 (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
      General note
      Contains handwritten annotation: "G Ray keep up the good work [Crocker]"
      Format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 45rpm
    - Machine & Hummer, "Introvert" [1]-- "room beyond the door" [2]-- "angel in rags", Undated (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
    - Squeegies, [1]-- "Don't Tread on Flowers" [2] -- "I Wanna Know Right Now", [1967] (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
    - Gary, Quazar, [1]-- "Suicide [2]-- Lesbian Boy; News, Undated (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
      Contains handwritten annotation: "Hey Gary, [Gary] Quazar"
    - Workdogs, [1]-- "Funny $" [2]-- "Last Friend's Gone", 1986 (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
      Format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 33 1/3 rpm
    - [Finis Coronat Opus (23) - A Jim Sharp Product], [1990] (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
      Contains handwritten annotation: "To Gary - Here's Comin' at Ya --- Jim S -- 12-15-90 1:45 AM Brooklyn"
      Plastikville Records. Side B is blank
      Format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 46rpm
- Series IV: Video Recordings
  This series contains video recordings of performances at Darinka. Access copies may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
  - Twad Schuetrum, 11/1/85 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0216)
    Format: VHS
  - Richard Kern, "Manhattan Love Suicides", 1985 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0206)
  - Gary Ray: It Comes In Waves (Rough Edit), c. 1986 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0202)
  - "The Doorman", 1987 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0205)
  - Jason Brandenburg, "Moonglow", 1987 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0208)
  - Jason Brandenburg, "Moonglow", [1987] (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0207)
  - Blind Double Date, 1989 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0201)
  - Theory of Total Blame, Rapp Art Center NYC: Karen Finley, June 18, 1989 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0215)
  - Church of the Little Green Man at Max Fish, 10/1990 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0203)
  - Czolgosz at PS122, c. 1990 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0204)
  - Gary Ray: Organic Extensionism, 5/16/92 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0209)
  - Biohazardous, 2001 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0200)
  - Gary Ray hosting AGA, 2003 (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0199)
  - "A Slice of Life," William Kent, Undated (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0213)
  - Chett Grant: A Portrait of the Man, Undated (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0212)
  - "Poison" (Rough Cut), Undated (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0210)
  - "Poltergash", Undated (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0211)
  - Milestone Film, "Spread the Word", Undated (Box 10, Cassette ID: 340.0214)
- Series V: Data Storage
  This series contains files and photographs, stored on computer disks.
  - Darinka - Misc. photos - NYC-LES-Performance, 1970's, 1980's, 1990's, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0001)
    Format: DVD-R
  - Darinka Bak - ML - World and USA File, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0002)
    Format: 5 1/4" DSDD Computer Disk
  - Darinka ML, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0003)
  - List, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0004)
  - Worldstar disk 6 - Advanced features, Mail list, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0005)
  - Copyiipc, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0006)
  - SOS Backup Dsk, 2-16-94, 20 pages, [1994] (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0007)
  - Play - early SOS, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0008)
  - Conn Bak-up - Saved, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0009)
  - Data on-file castbox, Undated (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0010)
- Oversize Series I: Darinka Files
  This series contains the oversize material from series I.
  - "Adam Bomb" lyric poster, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Carlo McCormick benefit poster, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Clay Spohn - Annotated bible 11/24/1916, Undated (Box 5, Object C)
  - Darinka stencils by Paul Chelstad, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - East Village Eye - blurb, September 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger / Karen Finley poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Factory / Market poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Gigantic - movie poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Head to the Future poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Issue of "Backstage", June 28, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Johanna Went poster and press release, June 9, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mike Osterhout "M" poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Misc. news articles, 1985, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "The New Common Good" article, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - New Ice Nights poster, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New York Newsday "City Living", April 4, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Nick Zedd's "School of Shame" poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Nick Zedd / B. Moran / R. Kern poster, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Observe poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Paper magazine, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photo album (black cover), Undated (Box 5, Photo-album A)
  - Photo album (red cover), Undated (Box 5, Photo-album B)
  - Soul Samurai poster, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Theory of Total Blame poster, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - These Showers Can Talk poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Tubby Boots" poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Village Voice - "East Side Confidential", November 13, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Village Voice - "Kitchen" article, March 5, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "When Lithuania Ruled the World part III" poster, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)